

#### **CONTACT ME AT**

- Address: Nadda, Dhaka-1212, Morol Bazar, Sarkar Bari.
- faraazhossainimran@gmail.com\_\_\_\_\_
- <u>www.imranhossain.com</u>

## SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• Html

•••• CSS/SASS

•••• JavaScript

•••• Bootstrap/Material UI

•••• Wordpress

Typing Speed(Wpm):Average: 64.3Top Speed: 96Link: Check Typing Stat

## AWARDS RECEIVED

100% Attendance award in HSC

# **IMRAN HOSSAIN**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a quick learner and a self-taught developer. I have been working on Javascript & related technologies for the past 2 years. Programming is my passion and I love to create things with my ideas. My other side is an entrepreneur and business enthusiast who enjoys finding technological solutions for people's problems.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Upwork

Web Developer | Aug 2020 - present

- Upgrade A website into Divi Page builders website.
- Improve some designs, fix technical problems, and audit the website.

## Steps Academic And Admission Care

Mentor and Coordinator | May 2018 - April 2020

- 1. Mentor class (9-10) in physics.
- 2. Managed Students, Teachers Payments, and attendance.

#### EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

#### Bangla College

BSC in Botnay | 2018 - 2022

### Dhaka Imperial College

Science | 2015 - 2017